var card = [
    {
        key : 0,
        question : "Which type of JavaScript language is ______ ?",
        option1 : "Object-Oriented",
        option2 : "Object-Based",
        option3 : "Assembly language",
        option4 : "High level",
        correct : "option2" 
    },
    {
        key : 1,
        question : "In JavaScript, what is a block of statement ?",
        option1 : "Conditional block",
        option2 : "both conditional block and a single statement",
        option3 : "block that combines a number of statements into a single compound statement",
        option4 : "block that contains a single statement",
        correct : "option3" 
    },
    {
        key : 2,
        question : "The \"function\" and \"var\" are known as:",
        option1 : "Keywords",
        option2 : "Data types",
        option3 : "Declaration statements",
        option4 : "Prototypes",
        correct : "option3" 
    },
    {
        key : 3,
        question : "Which of the following variables takes precedence over the others if the names are the same ?",
        option1 : "The local variable",
        option2 : "Global variable",
        option3 : "The two of the above",
        option4 : "None of the above",
        correct : "option1" 
    },
    {
        key : 4,
        question : "Which one of the following is the correct way for calling the JavaScript code ?",
        option1 : "Preprocessor",
        option2 : "Triggering Event",
        option3 : "RMI",
        option4 : "Function/Method",
        correct : "option4" 
    },
    {
        key : 5,
        question : "When there is an indefinite or an infinite value during an arithmetic computation in a program, then JavaScript prints ________",
        option1 : "Prints an exception error",
        option2 : "Prints an overflow error",
        option3 : "Displays \"Infinity\"",
        option4 : "Prints the value as such",
        correct : "option3" 
    },
    {
        key : 6,
        question : "In the JavaScript, which one of the following is not considered as an error: ",
        option1 : "Syntax error",
        option2 : "Missing of semicolons",
        option3 : "Missing of Bracket",
        option4 : "Division by zero",
        correct : "option4" 
    },
    {
        key : 7,
        question : "Choose the correct snippet from the following to check if the variable a is not equal the \"NULL\": ",
        option1 : "if(a!==null)",
        option2 : "if (a!)",
        option3 : "if(a!null)",
        option4 : "if(a!=null)",
        correct : "option1" 
    },
    {
        key : 8,
        question : "Which of the following are the features of an HTTP request ?",
        option1 : "URL being requested",
        option2 : "Optional request body",
        option3 : "Optional set of request headers",
        option4 : "All of the above",
        correct : "option4" 
    },
    {
        key : 9,
        question : " The localStorage and sessionStorage belongs to ___________ ",
        option1 : "Window object",
        option2 : "Element object",
        option3 : "DOM object",
        option4 : "Hash object",
        correct : "option1" 
    }
]